A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller photographs, Snapshot Files, RG 4 FA1128C
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Resorts (600), 1950-1990; 7
  - 600,092 (2) Hawaii; 834 Fifth Avenue, 1988 February (Box 22)
    One image of living room, 834 Fifth Avenue, NY.
  - 600,193 Caneel Bay, 1988 January (Box 22)
    Views, boats in bay. File includes one image of Fulla mosaic mural.
  - 600,194 Hawaii, 1989 (Box 22)
    Kahala Hilton, floral arrangements, MFR on balcony.
  - 600,195 Dorado Beach, 1987-1989 December (Box 22)
    LSR and MFR at Dorado Beach with Chi Chi Rodriguez and others.
  - 600,196 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel, 1990 (Box 22)
    LSR, MFR, and others by Buddha statue. Image used in Mauna Kea Newsletter.
  - 600,197 Caneel Bay, 1989 (Box 22)
  - 600,197 (A) Caneel Bay, 1989 (Box 22)
    Waletzky family.